{
    "Q1": {
        "question": "88",
        "answer1": "1",
        "answer2": "2",
        "answer3": "3",
        "rightAnswer": "3"
    },
    "Q2": {
        "question": "Salut c'est cool",
        "answer1": "oui",
        "answer2": "peut etre ",
        "answer3": "non",
        "rightAnswer": "non"
    },
    "Q3": {
        "question": "g f1",
        "answer1": "carrement",
        "answer2": "pas du tout ",
        "answer3": "un peu",
        "rightAnswer": "un peu"
    },
    "Q4": {
        "question": "5+5",
        "answer1": "10",
        "answer2": "6",
        "answer3": "7",
        "rightAnswer": "10"
    },
    "Q5": {
        "question": "42+1",
        "answer1": "43",
        "answer2": "56",
        "answer3": "37",
        "rightAnswer": "43"
    },
    "Q6": {
        "question": "salut mon petit ",
        "answer1": "non",
        "answer2": "oui ",
        "answer3": "peut etre",
        "rightAnswer": "oui"
    },
    "Q7": {
        "question": "cc",
        "answer1": "salug",
        "answer2": "cc",
        "answer3": "cc1",
        "rightAnswer": "cc"
    },
    "Q8": {
        "question": "test",
        "answer1": "77124",
        "answer2": "771A2",
        "answer3": "77",
        "rightAnswer": "77"
    },
    "Q9": {
        "question": "Madame",
        "answer1": "Monsieur",
        "answer2": "Madame",
        "answer3": "papa",
        "rightAnswer": "papa"
    },
    "Q10": {
        "question": "test",
        "answer1": "1",
        "answer2": "2",
        "answer3": "3",
        "rightAnswer": "2"
    }
}